Luiz Thiago Lira Diniz Rangel

Alcebiades da Cunha, 101 - APT 103 | João Pessoa/PB - Brazil, 58051-080 <u>Ithiagol@gmail.com</u> | +55 83 991 991 638 | linkedin.com/in/Ithiagol

About

Skilled **DevOps Engineer** experienced with Infrastructure as a Code (**Puppet** and **Terraform**) and system administration. Interested in integrating, deploying and sustaining applications maintained across on premise and cloud infrastructure. Looking for a position that's possible to maintain a solid and stable **CI/CD** pipeline allying various DevOps practices and tools like containerization, tasks automation (**SHELL** and **Python**), automated analysis, and other trendy technologies. **AWS Solutions Architect** certified with **10+ years** of experience with IT.

Education

Bachelor's degree - Computer Networks | 2010

Instituto Federal da Paraíba - IFPB, João Pessoa/PB

Graduated degree - Information Security | 2011

Faculdade De Tecnologia de João Pessoa - FATEC, João Pessoa/PB

Experience

2018 - Now | DevOps @ Reliant Solutions | New York/NY (Remote)

As a DevOps in a remote team, create Puppet code for various services provided by the company. Following good practices and interacting with the team with the main goal of delivering the best solutions as possible.

2017 - 2018 | DevOps @ Stefanini IT Solutions | Campina Grande/PB

Manage local development environment using Docker containers to maintaining the agile and flexibility between various teams. Through devops philosophy implement a fully automated continuous integration pipeline and change management, permitting reproducible and expandible infrastructure as a code.

2013 - 2016 | Infrastructure Coordinator @ Phoebus Tecnologia | João Pessoa/PB

Lead the infrastructure team in providing state of art networking services using Palo Alto Networks and Fortinet appliances, provide wide range of tasks automations using BASH/Python scripts and being part of committee to attend PCI-DSS requirements

2011 - 2013 | Infrastructure Analyst @ Unimed Campina Grande | Campina Grande/PB

Manage local private cloud (VMware based) and delivery IT infrastructure necessary for maintaining authentication and transactions for Healthcare insurance customers

2008 - 2011 | Sysadmin @ 6PS | Murfreesboro/TN (Remote)

Manage local all necessary network infrastructure to keep a small Hosting company working. Dealing with administration of pure Linux servers or with cPanel/WHM and Windows hosts for dedicated and shared hosting solutions.

Certifications

- → Certified Solutions Architect Associate Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- → Secure Cloud Services Exin
- → Cloud Computing Foundation Exin
- → Information Security Foundation, based on ISO/IEC 27002 Exin
- → ITIL Foundation Axelos
- → CloudU Rackspace